chenstai.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

**REGISTRATION**  
If you register on  chenstai.com B2B Network as a member, we collect and store all the information you enter. Our Membership Statistics, Industrial and Geographical classification statistics are derived from these information. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used by  chenstai.com B2B Network and certain members to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested.  
We also display certain information you enter on your specific company detail page including but not limited to: your company name, your first name and lastname and your job title.

 **REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS**  
If you register in chenstai.com B2B Network, you agree to:  
(a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself and the company you represent  
(b) provide your e-mail address, postal address, phone, fax, website address (url) ONLY on site sections and fields where we specifically ask for these details  
(c) maintain and promptly update the Registration Content to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete,  chenstai.com B2B Network has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete and  chenstai.com B2B Network reserves the right to suspend or terminate your member service.  
A global B2B network and your company information and any other publicly available information you provide on chenstai.com (including but not limited to: your company name, your first name and lastname and your job title) may appear on other chenstai.com partner sites.  
Your  chenstai.com B2B Network Account Information and Member Profile are password-protected so that other  chenstai.com B2B Network members and / or third parties will not have the ability to access, edit or delete this personal information. Any password protection system may be vulnerable to certain attacks, and therefore  chenstai.com B2B Network cannot 100% guarantee the protection of your personal information from malicious third parties. We recommend you to do not disclose your password to anyone and change your password from time to time.

 **PUBLISHING INFORMATION**  
Company Description, Trade Lead Publishing and Product Detail Publishing:  
All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on  chenstai.com B2B Network and therefore accessible by visitors, certain robots and members. The publicly available information can be also cached by search engines and robots and -as we do have no control over these entities- we can not influence the way these details are presented on certain pages / sites / etc. If you ever request your pages to be removed from our sites and servers we will do this but it is your responsibilitry to remove the publicly available information from any third party.  
Any Publishing Information that you use on  chenstai.com B2B Network forms becomes public information and you respond for them (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights).  
If you submit any information to  chenstai.com B2B Network to be published on our B2B Network through the publishing forms you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.

 **COOKIES**  
chenstai.com B2B Network uses cookies only to maintain your information as you move throughout this site and facilitate your member activities. A cookie is a small piece of information used to identify an individual when the person is accessing a site. Cookies are used only for the intended purpose and scope of  chenstai.com B2B Network.  
Cookies and the tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to this site, and understanding how visitors use this site. Cookies can also help customize this site for visitors. If you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. This site or the advertisers on this site may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.

 **INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**  
chenstai.com B2B Network does not disclose the collected information (except the Publishing Information) to any third parties, unless acting under the belief that such action is necessary to:  
(a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of  chenstai.com B2B Network  
(c) act to protect the interests of its members or others.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information to authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of  chenstai.com B2B Network, our members, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information in response to a judicial order or when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

chenstai.com B2B Network considers and respects an individual's privacy seriously and importantly. The services we provide require that we collect, process, use, display and distribute certain details you provide us. Therefore,  chenstai.com B2B Network does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. If you would like to remove your Company please Contact Us.

We welcome your additional input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you.
